# **CURRICULUM VITAE**



JANARDHAN BURDE Sr.StoreExecutive Total Experience -13 +Years

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Seeking a challenging store management position where I can utilize my 13+ years of experience as Store contribute manager to management/leadership and interpersonal skills to the benefit of the organization. Storage, handling and accounting of wide verity of items normally used in Construction.

Constructions Bulk Materials:- Aggregate, Sand, Steel, Cement, Diesel, Bitumen, Emulation, Chemical, Oil/Lubricants and Spare parts, Electrical materials, Plumbing materials Hardware and consumables, Assets, shuttering and scaffolding materials, Rmc/Crusher Production inventory Etc.

## CONTACT- 8408001545/7666681645

# My profile :

www.linkedin.com/in/arvind-burdewww.Naukri.com & Facebook.com

**EMAIL:** arvind.burde1983@gmail.com

**Lack Example 24-08-1983** 

🗼 Nationality:- Indian

Languages Known:- Hindi, English, Marathi

Gender: - Male

Hobbies: - Playing cricket, Captain of a team

↓ India Driving License: -Indian Union Driving License S.no: MP05N- 2013-0051516.

**+** 

Current Salary:- 32000/ 3,84,000 CTC

# **EDUCATION**

•

B.Com from RTM Nagpur University in 2006



HSC from Samarth College Lakhani in 2001



SSC from Vinod Vidyalaya, Tekepar in 1999



TALLY from Globe Institute, Bhandara in 2006



# **WORK EXPERIENCE**



## F-Period: 01 July 2023 Till date

Company : SMS Infrastructure Ltd. Nagpur
Designation : Store Officer – SAP MM

Department : Stores

Project Name : 6-Laning of Section of Bharatmala

**Durg - Arung Bypass Expressway (CG)** 

Client : National Highways Authority of India.

Location : Utai,Patan Durg (CG)

Cost of Project : 789 Crores.



#### E-Period: 05 Oct 2021 to 30 June 2023

Company : PGS INDIA PVT, LTD, Mumbai

Designation : Store Incharge
Department : Store & Purchase

Project Name : Amrawati-Chikhli Road Project MH.

Client : Eagle Infra India ltd.

Type of Project : Flyover & Major Bridges constructions

Cost of Project : 100 Crores.

Location : Ridhora Bypass, Akola, Maharashtra

Lenth Of Project : 40 Kms.

## 4

#### D-Period : 24 Oct 2017 to 30 Sept 2021

Company : Mep Infra & Deve. Ltd. Mumbai

Designation : Executive store.

Department : Stores & Purchase

Project Name : Hingna- Kamthi Road Project

Client : NHAI.

Location : Khadgaon Plant, Nagpur, Maharashtra
Type of construction : Outer ring road Rigid Pavements

Length of Project : 61Kms.

Cost of Project : 1100 Crores.



### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Construction/Engineering/Cement/Metals.
- Logistics/Supply chain
- Store Keeper/Store Incharge/Purchase
- Railway Projects
- Building Projects
- Lift Irrigation Project
- Power sub-station project
- Flyover and Major Bridges Project
- National Highway/Pwd Road Projects.

## STORE INVENTORY MANAGEMENT

- INWORD: It can be explained a register keeping track of all the goods inward. Whenever Goods Track from supplier enters premises of the Organisation, an entry is made in the inward register to record time and date of inward of goods. Some organisations even record the truck registration no, Name of the driver.
- → GRN: Maintaining record of goods received at the point of receipt. This record is used to confirm all goods have been received and often compared to a purchase order before payments is issued.
- Ledger register: this provides the information regarding the order of material and cumulative quantity of material till date.
- → Daily material report: this report gives information regarding daily material consumption stock available for further use for the project.
- Running amount bill: this is very important part data which gives the actual executed quantities required for the project.
- **ABC** Analysis.
- All materials will be issued on First-in-First Out (FIFO)

## **PURCHASE**

- Receipt and Verification of Purchase indents from user departments, through Stores/Site.
- Vendor Development & Registering into System.
- Obtaining of Quotations from various Vendors.
- Survey of Market rates & tracking into system.
- Preparation of Comparative Statements.
- Negotiate with Vendors for pricing, Payment terms & lead-time, terms/conditions etc.
- Preparation & Issue of Purchase orders.
- Maintain of Status Reports.
- Co-ordination with Stores, Purchase & Accounts Personnel's.
- Follow-up with Vendor for Timely delivery of Material.
- Follow-up with Accounts Personnel s for timely releasing the Payments.

#### 4 C-Period: 16 Dec 2016 to 15 Oct 2017

Company : DP Jain Infra Pvt. Ltd. Nagpur

Designation : Executive store.

Department : Stores

Project Name : Sagar Lakhandon Road Project

Client : NHAI.

Location : Titarpani Toll Plaza, Maharajpur, MP
Type of construction : Toll & Maintenance Road Project

Length of Project : 137Kms.

### **♣** B-Period : 18 May 2013 to 15 Dec 2016

Company : DP Jain Infra Pvt. Ltd.

Designation : Executive Store.

Department : Stores

Project Name : Tedhwa Seoni Lift Irrigation Project

Client : PWD Maharashtra

Location : Tedhwa, Gondia, Maharashtra

Type of construction: Civil works of Pump

House,Pier,Retaing Wall and Switchyard and Rising Main

Cost of Project : 80Crores.

#### A-Period: 01 Sept 2007 to 30 April 2013

Company : Ashoka Buildcon Ltd. Nashik

Designation : Stores Keeper

Department : Stores

Project name : Durg-Bhandara 4-Lane of NH-6 BOT Road Project

Client : NHAI

Location : Lakhani Camp NH-6 Maharashtra

Type of construction : Flexible Pavement Road Project

Cost of Project : 1200 Crores.

# **SKILLS**

- Good communication skills.
- 🖶 Bookkeeping skills.
- Excellent customer service and interpersonal skills.
- Analytical and problem solving skills.
- **4** Ability to gather and analyze data and to work with figure.
- Leading & Supervising
- Team working skills.
- Vendor Relationships.
- 🖶 Good knowledge of building methods and regulations

# **Computer Skills**

- Microsoft office all versions.
- ∔ TALLY ERP
- **SAP MM Module. 740 version 7400.3.8.1123**
- XPEDEON ERP (Enterprise Resource Planning).

### KNOWLEDGE

- Patience and the ability to remain calm in Stressful situations.
- The ability to accept criticism and work Well under pressure.
- To enjoy working with other people.
- Sensitivity and understanding.

## MAJAR INDUSTRIAL MATERIALS

#### **Civil & Mechanical Store**

- Building Materials
- Scaffolding & Shuttering Materials
- Electrical Materials
- Survey & Civil Instruments
- Safety Materials
- 🖶 Hardware & General Materials
- 🖶 Tools & Machinery
- Spare parts & Lubricants
- 📤 Lab Equipments
- 🖶 Plumbing Materials
- 🖶 Household Materials
- Assets Materials

#### **Materials Reconciliation & Reporting**

- DPR, MPR, Debit Note & Credit Note
- Hire Machinery Billing
- Transportation Billing
- Diesel reconciliation
- Steel,Cement,Aggregate reconcilation
- Sub-contractor materials inventory
- Employee materials inventory
- 🖶 Weigh Bridge Monitoring
- Measurement
- Royalty record
  - Vendor Development
- & WBS structure
- 🚣 Material physical
- Rmc Production
- Crusher Production
- Reporting to PM,GM,Purchase,Account & HO

#### PRESENT ADDRESS

#### SMS INFRA LTD

Near Mohanlal Motors , Utai Squre, Dumardih Patan Road, Durg , Chhattisgarh

Utai - 491107

### PREMANENT ADDRESS

Arvind J Burde . At Post Amgaon (Dighori)

Tah. & Dist.Bhandara, Maharashtra

Pin code - 441804

#### DECLARATION

# JOB RESPONSIBILITIES

- ♣ Knowledge of the PR/PO/GRN/STO/In-transit/E-way Bill Reservation on regular basis itself as per requirement.
- **♣** Knowledge of stock statement report SAP MM physicalstock plant wise/storage wise/Group wise on every month.
- Reconciliation of all major material stock with Account/ Planning Department on every month.
- Preparing & review the monthly MIS reports as per specific format.
- Monitoring & checking of all transaction reason for a moment on regularly.
- ♣ Preparing Inward & outward registers for every day and as well as check with the security register.
- Preparing the sub-contractor material issuing record / Material reconciliation / Debit Note / Credit Note on every month and submitting to Billing & Budgeting or accounts department.
- → Designated in store of storage area for materials Inspection/Rejection/FOC/repairing zone.
- ♣ Preparing of supply materials as per BOQ and certification by sequential/MRC from the client.
- Preparing of HSD transaction report SAP MM Physical.
- Procurement plan of spares and other consumables material according to Project requirements.
- Preparation of DMR, reports of Bulk material as per specific format
- Maintain the Fixed Assets and minor equipment report on every month.
- ♣ Keep the material type-wise / group-wise / Item wise materials in roe rack bin with a display board.
- Checked every day trip-wise record security & weighbridge & sap of aggregate, cement, flyash & etc. When the material is received on the site/plant.
- Control the material where material not required, Material issued from store only authorized person.
- Excess / Shortage material found during receiving immediately informed to CO/HO/Purchaser.
- Knowledge in all construction machinery monthly billing.
- Knowledge in the Concrete grade-wise consumption as per mix design.
- Maintained separately of shuttering material record & every month
- Material Received with Proper Identifications with necessary documents.
- Responsibilities of a fully computerized an SAP MM, construction stores.
- Condition monitoring, maintaining minimum & maximum level of critical & fast-moving items.
- Maintaining FIFO system, maintaining all stores documents (stock ledger, Dmr etc).
- ♣ Ensure that the assets received from sites to Central stores will get refurbished in advance & keep ready for dispatch on demand.

I hereby, declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date:-

Place:-